Hello friend, I am Chandan Patel and
today I am going to talk
about ICICI Lumba General Insurance.
This company is very good and
it belongs to ICI. Before Covid,
listen carefully. Before Covid, this stock had
performed very well but when Covid
came, this stock was beaten so badly
that you cannot imagine. Every
stock was beaten but ICI
Lumba was beaten very badly and if I talk about it, the
current price of this stock is
₹1,197.90 paise. In 1 year, it has
given a return of about 33 per cent, approximately
4453. And if I talk about 5 years here, then there is
not that much return in the last 5 years. You can see here that
it had fallen below 1000.
Look, the stock had fallen below 1000.
How badly this stock was beaten and if I
show the chart of the maximum, then its IPO
opened in 2017, the approximate average price that is
coming is
80.20.
Money and till now from 2017 till now this stock has
given a return of 165%, so
if you look at it from a long term purpose then
this stock is very good for you and
in the future such stocks will dominate
and now if you look at this stock then
gradually in one month this stock has
given a return of approximately 125%, so you should definitely keep an eye on this stock,
thank you.